Your Majesty, is something bothering you?
Where is Cangyue?
I don't know.
These past few days,
Lady Cangyue has been acting very mysteriously.
I reckon she's probably been at the little prince's place.
Insolent!
How dare she!
Dismissed.
If you have the guts, don't ever come back!
I didn't expect the protagonist of this project
to have such a tragic background.
Feeling sorry for him?
Well,
Not really.
I'm just a little curious.
His Majesty died early.
Ah, no.
The late Emperor died early.
The Grand Princess supported His Majesty
after he ascended the throne at a young age,
and ruled from behind the curtain for many years.
To make him lose the support of the people,
she indeed forced him to do many bad things.
His background is truly tragic.
But he's just an NPC.
No need to feel sorry for him.
But your feelings for the young prince
seem quite deep too.
Isn't he also an NPC?
He's different.
Jingyuan.
Why do I feel like
what you're experiencing
isn't the lost emotion recovery project?
Tell me the truth.
Does this game have other ways to play
different from its public promotion?
You don't look like
someone who has lost their emotions.
You caught me.
I have too many emotions,
so I came here to date.
Date? With whom?
With you.
Me?
I couldn't tell.
Miss Cangyue has very unique taste.
Si Xingxuan.
I...
Why aren't you wearing the hairpin I gave you?
I have too many hairpins.
I can't wear them all.
What are you doing?
Now they are gone.
Can you wear it now?
This is a gift from Jingyuan.
A gift?
You can wear the gift he gave you,
but not the gift I gave you?
That day with me,
you were still baring your heart.
Today you are with another man,
drinking tea, chatting, and being romantic.
Your Majesty, don't scare her.
Eunuch Jingyuan is truly kind-hearted.
No wonder he is so popular.
If he was thrown into the celestial prison,
he would be even more popular.
Si Xingxuan,
how can you say that?
Jing Yuan is our friend.
Does a servant deserve to be my friend?
A servant?
If he's a servant,
have you ever thought,
that I am also just
a servant by your side?
You are different.
There is no hierarchy between us.
How am I different?
Then what are we?
We are partners.
So you are nothing but
a pawn used by His Majesty.
Unlike me.
I truly wanted to be friends with Cang Yue.
Say one more word,
and I will kill you.
Si Xingxuan, let go of me.
What are you doing?
Let go right now.
Let go.
You're actually defending him.
Fine.
Sister Xiaoyue.
Brother, why do you have wrinkles on your face again?
Sister Xiaoyue, look.
Pixiu had puppies.
But they look exactly the same.
Yes, they look the same.
This way, even if I lose one,
I still have another.
I wish I had two brothers.
That way, even if one dies,
I would still have another.
Actually, my brother is very lonely.
I have seen him
spacing out in the study several times.
But since you came,
he started smiling.
Is he really lonely?